[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "яблоко",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "red",
        "back": "красный",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "grey",
        "back": "серый",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "lemon",
        "back": "лимон",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "pie",
        "back": "пирог",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "green",
        "back": "зелёный"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "black",
        "back": "чёрный",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "milk",
        "back": "молоко",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "white",
        "back": "белый",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "meat",
        "back": "мясо",
        "setName": "English"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "margin",
        "back": "отступ внешний",
        "setName": "css-свойства"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "padding",
        "back": "внутренний отступ",
        "setName": "css-свойства"
    }
]